KUBASU IVAN SAKWA

Tel: +254114872974 | Email: kubasuivansakwa23@gmail.com | Nairobi

LinkedIn: Kubasu Ivan Sakwa GitHub: Kubasu Ivan Sakwa

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated front-end web developer with a relentless passion for crafting immersive and user-centric digital experiences. With 2 years of experience, I have honed my skills to transform design concepts into elegant, responsive, and intuitive web applications.

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

JavaScript | React | Tailwind CSS | Git | Debugging | Linux adept | Project Management | Teamwork & Collaboration | Creative Problem Solving | Excellent Communication Skills | Ability to learn fast

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer | September 2023 – present

Mutable-Tech – startup

A startup that is built around making software solutions affordable

Key contributions:

- Drafting software solutions
- Working on React and Tailwind code bases for the frontend
- Writing tests
- Debugging software code
- Managing and updating companies code base on GitHub

 Worked with backend developers to implement API's and Databases to the Client side

Open-Source Contribution | 2021 - present

GitHub

 Contribution to GitHub open-source projects such as remix-run and Zetech 's university open-source projects

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Zetech University | 2021 - present

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

St Luke's Highschool | Jan 2020 - April 2021. Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (Grade: C+)

Next of Kin

- Harnes Mukhongo - Dad

0721486339

REFEREES

Suzan Kamau +254 717 208462 kamausuzan711@gmail.com Ruperth Nyagesoa +254 748 223452 ruperthnyagesoa@gmail.com